Guide to the John M. Meek Collection
John M. Meek Collection 1934-1999 1967-1968
- Maps, 1934-1999; id1099869; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_0000_0000
  - id1099870 (Folder 1)
    - Plot Plan for International Amphitheatre, Stockyard Inn, Chicago, Illinois, 1968; id1099871; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_1 (Folder 1)
      78" x 33"
    - International Amphitheatre Press Seating, 1956; id1099872; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_2 (Folder 1)
      24.5" x 17"
    - General Amphitheatre Plan View, 1956; id1099873; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_3 (Folder 1)
      22" x 17.5"
    - Lecturn Elevation View & Press Line of Sight, 1956; id1099874; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_4 (Folder 1)
    - Balcony Platform & Sight Lines, 1956; id1099875; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_5 (Folder 1)
    - Conrad Hilton Hotel, Exhibition Hall, Space Allocation, 1956; id1099876; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_6 (Folder 1)
      18" x 14"
    - International Amphitheatre Exposition Hall, 1968; id1099877; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_7 (Folder 1)
      42" x 30"
    - International Amphitheatre CBS News Special Events Unit, 1968; id1099878; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_8 (Folder 1)
      25" x 21"
    - Democratic National Convention, International Amphitheatre, 1968; id1099879; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_9 (Folder 1)
      11" x 10.5"
    - International Amphitheatre, Second Floor Plan, 1968; id1099880; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_10 (Folder 1)
      16" x 11"
    - International Amphitheatre, 1968; id1099881; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_11 (Folder 1)
      24" x 20"
    - International Amphitheatre Broadcasters Space Allocation Layout, 1967; id1099882; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_12 (Folder 1)
      53.5" x 17.5"
    - International Amphitheatre, Proposed Broadcasters Work Space, 1967; id1099883; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_13 (Folder 1)
      29" x 9"
    - Preliminary Conception Drawing of Network Anchor Booth Locations for Democratic National Convention, 1968; id1099884; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_14 (Folder 1)
      27" x 35"
    - International Amphitheatre, undated; id1099885; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_15 (Folder 1)
      52" x 17"
    - Proposed Space Assignment, 1968; id1099886; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_16 (Folder 1)
      54" x 17"
    - International Amphitheatre, Second Floor Plan, 1940; id1099887; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_17 (Folder 1)
      45.5" x 30"
    - International Amphitheatre, Section Views, 1934; id1099888; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_18 (Folder 1)
      42" x 27.5"
    - International Amphitheatre, Balcony Seating Plan, undated; id1099889; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_19 (Folder 1)
      43" x 35"
    - International Amphitheatre, undated; id1099890; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_20 (Folder 1)
      22" x 17"
    - International Amphitheatre, Republican Convention, 1960; id1099891; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_21 (Folder 1)
      42" x 31"
    - International Amphitheatre, First Floor, Arena Section, South Wing, 1948; id1099892; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_22 (Folder 1)
      29" x 19"
    - International Amphitheatre, Second Floor, North Wing, 1936; id1099893; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_23 (Folder 1)
      28" x 18.5"
    - International Amphitheatre, First Floor, North Wing, 1936; id1099894; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_23B (Folder 1)
    - International Amphitheatre, Second Floor, South Wing, 1947; id1099895; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_24 (Folder 1)
      28" x 19"
    - International Amphitheatre, First Floor, South Wing, 1936; id1099896; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_25 (Folder 1)
    - International Amphitheatre, undated; id1099897; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_26 (Folder 1)
    - International Amphitheatre, Exposition Hall, undated; id1099898; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_27 (Folder 1)
      21" x 13"
    - International Amphitheatre, Second Floor Plan, 1940; id1099899; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_28 (Folder 1)
      16" x 10.5"
    - International Amphitheatre, First Floor Plan, 1939; id1099900; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_29 (Folder 1)
      17" x 11"
    - International Amphitheatre, Exposition Hall, undated; id1099901; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_30 (Folder 1)
      40" x 30"
    - International Amphitheatre, Second Floor Plan, undated; id1099902; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_31 (Folder 1)
      40" x 24.75"
    - International Amphitheatre, Seating Plan, Main floor, Mezzanine, and Balcony, undated; id1099903; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_32 (Folder 1)
    - International Amphitheatre, South Hall, 1968; id1099904; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_33 (Folder 1)
      39" x 30"
    - International Amphitheatre, Exposition Hall, 1968; id1099905; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_1_34 (Folder 1)
      30" x 42.5"
  - id1099906 (Folder 2)
    - Large tally sheet for 1968 convention state delegation, id1099907; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_1 (Folder 2)
      32" x 27"
    - Illinois Bell Telephone Company, Daily Convention Directory, 1968; id1099908; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_2A (Folder 2)
      12" x 12"
    - Illinois Bell Telephone Company, Daily Convention Directory, 1968; id1099909; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_0000_2B (Folder 2)
    - Map of seating at Amphitheatre, undated; id1099910; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_3 (Folder 2)
      11" x 24"
    - Ground floor plans for expansion of Convention Hall, Miami Beach, 1966; id1099911; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_4 (Folder 2)
      18" x 12"
    - Seating Arrangement for Democratic National Convention, Miami Beach, [1967]; id1099912; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_5A (Folder 2)
      42" x 36"
    - Seating Arrangement for Democratic National Convention, Miami Beach, [1967]; id1099913; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_0000_5B (Folder 2)
    - Various maps of hotels located near Convention Hall, [1967]; id1099914; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_6A (Folder 2)
    - Various maps of hotels located near Convention Hall, [1967]; id1099915; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_0000_7B (Folder 2)
    - Expansion of Commuter Hall, 1967; id1099916; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_7A (Folder 2)
      22" x 18"
    - Basement Plan of Conrad Hilton Hotel, Chicago, undated; id1099917; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_8A (Folder 2)
      32" x 15"
    - Basement Plan of Conrad Hilton Hotel, Chicago, undated; id1099918; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_0000_8B (Folder 2)
    - Ground Plat Southeast Corner-Halsted & Exchange, 1939; id1099919; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_9 (Folder 2)
      24.5" x 24.5"
    - Space Allocation for Democratic National Convention, 1956; id1099920; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_10 (Folder 2)
    - Work Space at Exhibition Hall, Conrad Hilton Hotel, 1956; id1099921; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_11 (Folder 2)
      17.5" x 19.5"
    - Presidential Suite, 2nd Floor, Boys' and Girls' Club Building, Stockyard Inn, 1968; id1099922; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_12 (Folder 2)
      32.5" x 23"
    - Advertising fold-out for Los Angeles Memorial Sports Arena, undated; id1099923; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_13 (Folder 2)
    - Peristyle Platforming Plan View, Democratic Convention, 1960; id1099924; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_14 (Folder 2)
      24" x 22.5"
    - Los Angeles Sports Arena, Seating, 1959; id1099925; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_15 (Folder 2)
      29" x 20"
    - Alterations to Sports Arena for Democratic National Convention, 1960; id1099926; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_16 (Folder 2)
      35.5" x 30.5"
    - Democratic National Convention, Delegate Seating Plan, 1960; id1099927; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_2_17 (Folder 2)
      17.5" x 9"
- Photographs, 1952-1993; id1099928; CAC_PP_068_4_0000_0000_0000
  This series consists of 213 items.
  - Close-up of John Martin Meek, undated; id1099930; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_1 (Box 1)
  - International Amphitheater, undated; id1099931; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_2a (Box 1)
  - International Amphitheater, undated; id1099932; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_2b (Box 1)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1952; id1099933; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_3 (Box 1)
  - Illinois Bell Telephone Company's "Dandy Dem" and anti-strike captions, 1968; id1099934; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_4a (Box 1)
  - Illinois Bell Telephone Company's "Dandy Dem" and anti-strike captions, 1968; id1099935; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_4b (Box 1)
  - Illinois Bell Telephone Company's "Dandy Dem" and anti-strike captions, 1968; id1099936; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_4c (Box 1)
  - Hotels and hotel signs in Houston, 1967; id1099937; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_5a (Box 1)
  - Hotels and hotel signs in Houston, 1967; id1099938; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_5b (Box 1)
  - Hotels and hotel signs in Houston, 1967; id1099939; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_5c (Box 1)
  - Hotels and hotel signs in Houston, 1967; id1099940; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_5d (Box 1)
  - Hotels and hotel signs in Houston, 1967; id1099941; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_5e (Box 1)
  - Hotels and hotel signs in Houston, 1967; id1099942; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_5f (Box 1)
  - Inside the Astrodome, 1967; id1099943; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_6a (Box 1)
  - Inside the Astrodome, 1967; id1099944; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_6b (Box 1)
  - Inside the Astrodome, 1967; id1099945; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_6c (Box 1)
  - Inside the Astrodome, 1967; id1099946; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_6d (Box 1)
  - Inside the Astrodome, 1967; id1099947; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_6e (Box 1)
  - DNC Site Selection Committee visiting NASA Manned Spacecraft Center in Houston, 1967; id1099948; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_7a (Box 1)
  - DNC Site Selection Committee visiting NASA Manned Spacecraft Center in Houston, 1967; id1099949; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_7b (Box 1)
  - DNC Site Selection Committee visiting NASA Manned Spacecraft Center in Houston, 1967; id1099950; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_7c (Box 1)
  - DNC Site Selection Committee visiting NASA Manned Spacecraft Center in Houston, 1967; id1099951; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_7d (Box 1)
  - DNC Site Selection Committee visiting NASA Manned Spacecraft Center in Houston, 1967; id1099952; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_7e (Box 1)
  - Camera Stands, 1968; id1099953; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_8a (Box 1)
  - Camera Stands, 1968; id1099954; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_8b (Box 1)
  - John Meek at a Cor-Plex preview, 1968; id1099955; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_9 (Box 1)
  - The "Perambulator," a camera device, 1968; id1099956; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_10 (Box 1)
  - AstroWorld's Manager, Designer, Roy Hofheinz (owner), and the Hofheinz family, 1967; id1099957; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_11a (Box 1)
  - AstroWorld's Manager, Designer, Roy Hofheinz (owner), and the Hofheinz family, 1967; id1099958; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_11b (Box 1)
  - AstroWorld's Manager, Designer, Roy Hofheinz (owner), and the Hofheinz family, 1967; id1099959; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_11c (Box 1)
  - AstroWorld's Manager, Designer, Roy Hofheinz (owner), and the Hofheinz family, 1967; id1099960; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_11d (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099961; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12a (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099962; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12b (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099963; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12c (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099964; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12d (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099965; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12e (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099966; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12f (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099967; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12g (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099968; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12h (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099969; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12i (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099970; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12j (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099971; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12k (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099972; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12l (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099973; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12m (Box 1)
  - Drawings and models, as well as actual construction photos of AstroWorld, 1967; id1099974; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_12n (Box 1)
  - The Forum in Los Angeles, 1967; id1099975; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_13 (Box 1)
  - Convention hall in Chicago, site of the 1944 Democratic Convention, undated; id1099976; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_14 (Box 1)
  - Jim Hartz of Tulsa, former host of NBC's "Today Show," second from the right with friends, 1991; id1099977; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_15 (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099978; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16a (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099979; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16b (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099980; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16c (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099981; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16d (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099982; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16e (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099983; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16f (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099984; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16g (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099985; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16h (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099986; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16i (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099987; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16j (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099988; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16k (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099989; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16l (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099990; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16m (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099991; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16n (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099992; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16o (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099993; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16p (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099994; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16q (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099995; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16r (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Transition Offices, 1992; id1099996; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_16s (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1099997; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17a (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1099998; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17b (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1099999; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17c (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100000; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17d (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100001; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17e (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100002; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17f (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100003; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17g (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100004; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17h (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100005; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17i (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100006; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17j (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100007; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17k (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100008; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17l (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100009; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17m (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100010; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17n (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100011; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17o (Box 1)
  - The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band performing in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100012; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_17p (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100013; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18a (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100014; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18b (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100015; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18c (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100016; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18d (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100017; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18e (Box 1)
  - John Martin Meek with Jane Demarines, 1992; id1100018; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18f (Box 1)
  - Judy Woodruff, CNN, 1992; id1100019; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18g (Box 1)
  - Molly Ivins, 1992; id1100020; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18h (Box 1)
  - Molly Ivins, 1992; id1100021; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18i (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100022; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18j (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100023; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18k (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100024; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18l (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100025; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18m (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100026; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18n (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100027; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18o (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100028; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18p (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100029; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18q (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100030; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18r (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100031; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18s (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100032; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18t (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100033; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18u (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100034; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18v (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100035; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18w (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100036; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18x (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night in Little Rock, Arkansas, 1992; id1100037; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_18y (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night, 1992; id1100038; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_19a (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night, 1992; id1100039; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_19b (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night, 1992; id1100040; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_19c (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night, 1992; id1100041; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_19d (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night, 1992; id1100042; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_19e (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night, 1992; id1100043; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_19f (Box 1)
  - John Martin Meek, 1992; id1100044; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_19g (Box 1)
  - John Martin Meek, 1992; id1100045; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_19h (Box 1)
  - John Martin Meek, 1992; id1100046; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_19i (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Election Night, 1992; id1100047; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_19j (Box 1)
  - The Old State Capitol building, 1992; id1100048; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20a (Box 1)
  - Wolf Blitzer, CNN, 1992; id1100049; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20b (Box 1)
  - Wolf Blitzer, CNN, 1992; id1100050; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20c (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100051; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20d (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100052; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20e (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100053; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20f (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100054; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20g (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100055; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20h (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100056; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20i (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100057; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20j (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100058; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20k (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100059; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20l (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100060; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20m (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100061; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20n (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100062; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20o (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100063; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20p (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100064; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20q (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100065; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20r (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100066; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20s (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100067; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20t (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100068; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20u (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100069; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20v (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100070; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20w (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100071; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20x (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100072; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20y (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100073; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20z (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100074; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20aa (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100075; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ab (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100076; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ac (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100077; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ad (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100078; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ae (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100079; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20af (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100080; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ag (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100081; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ah (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100082; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ai (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100083; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20aj (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100084; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ak (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100085; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20al (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100086; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20am (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100087; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20an (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100088; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ao (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100089; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ap (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100090; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20aq (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100091; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ar (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100092; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20as (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100093; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20at (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100094; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20au (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100095; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20av (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100096; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20aw (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100097; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ax (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100098; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ay (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100099; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20az (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100100; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20ba (Box 1)
  - Democratic Congressional Leaders, 1992; id1100101; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_20bb (Box 1)
  - Former Oklahoma Governor George Nigh, 1993; id1100102; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_21a (Box 1)